{
      "culture": "Vietnamese",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionNum": 1,
          "question": "How do you say 'Thank you' in Vietnamese?",
          "options": ["Cảm Ơn", "Xin Loi", "Taam Byeet"],
          "correctAnswer": "Cảm Ơn"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 2,
          "question": "How do you say 'Please' in Vietnamese?",
          "options": ["Vui Lòng", "sin loy", "dep"],
          "correctAnswer": "Vui Lòng"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 3,
          "question": "How do you say 'Excuse me' in Vietnamese?",
          "options": ["Gam-um", "Xin Lỗi", "comb"],
          "correctAnswer": "Xin Lỗi"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 4,
          "question": "How do you say 'Yes' in Vietnamese? ",
          "options": ["Da", "Zin chow", "comb"],
          "correctAnswer": "Da"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 5,
          "question": "How do you say 'No' in Vietnamese?",
          "options": ["yah", "Không", "Gam-um"],
          "correctAnswer": "Không"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 6,
          "question": "How do you say 'Nice to meet you' in Vietnamese?",
          "options": ["Rất vui được gặp bạn", "tạm biệt", "dep"],
          "correctAnswer": "Rất vui được gặp bạn"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 7,
          "question": "How do you say 'Goodbye' in Vietnamese? ",
          "options": ["tạm biệt", "", "choe song ham ni da"],
          "correctAnswer": "Shil lye ham ni da"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 8,
          "question": "What is a common way to apologize in Korean?",
          "options": ["Mi am ham ni da", "Shil lye ham ni da", "choe song ham ni da"],
          "correctAnswer": "Shil lye ham ni da"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 9,
          "question": "What is a common way to apologize in Korean?",
          "options": ["Mi am ham ni da", "Shil lye ham ni da", "choe song ham ni da"],
          "correctAnswer": "Shil lye ham ni da"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 10,
          "question": "What is a common way to apologize in Korean?",
          "options": ["Mi am ham ni da", "Shil lye ham ni da", "choe song ham ni da"],
          "correctAnswer": "Shil lye ham ni da"
        }
      ]
    }